Arnold Bustamante

UX/UI Designer

ArnoldBustamante.com | Linkedin.com/in/Arnold-Bustamante ArnoldBustamante@Gmail.com | (718)730-0827 New York, NY

PROFILE

UX/UI Designer proficient in UX research and visual design. With over 8 years of customer service experience, was able to develop a deep knowledge in user empathy, team collaboration and strategic thinking. Also has a strong background in acting and improv.

EXPERIENCE

Bloc Immersive UX/UI Program

UX/UI Designer

Dec 2019 - Jun 2020

- Alongside a senior product designer, learned industry best practices and design process standards with a focus on UX Research, Visual Design, and Front-end development.
- Produced a clickable prototype of a cloud file management app dedicated to empowering filmmakers.
- Created a solution that allowed users of a public transit app to know what time a certain bus was arriving at a certain station.
- Conducted both in-person and remote usability tests in order to enhance the usability and functionality of a project.

The Meatball Shop

Bartender

Oct 2015 - Dec 2019

- Increase sales by utilizing data acquired through customer interactions.
- Employed strategic thinking to solve any customer problems, complaints or concerns.
- Responsible for training and mentoring new employees.

Banana Republic

Cashier/ Sales Associate

Nov 2012 - Oct 2015

- Served multiple customers, discovered their needs, and made recommendations to generate sales.
- Collaborated with managers and team members to achieve the company's daily sales goals.
- Maintained knowledge of styling trends to better satisfy guest needs.
- Facilitated customer on-boarding process by establishing new accounts. Clearly communicated corporate policies & procedures.

SKILLS

UX & UI

Surveys • Interviews
• Competitive
analysis • User
stories • Personas •
User flows • Site
maps • Usability
testing • Branding •
Wireframing •
Prototyping

Software

Figma • Whimsical • Atom • Github

Development

HTML • CSS • Basic Javascript • Basic JQuery

EDUCATION

Queens College

Sep 2011 - Apr 2012

30 credits towards a bachelor degree.